

### **Brand Statement**

A Queens-based UX designer and illustrator. I am capable of bringing together a complex array of design elements and client feedback to create high quality, professional work. My goal is to continue to tackle bigger and more challenging projects in order to further my experiences and career.

jaeilchoart@gmail.com  $>\!\!<$ 

www.jaeilcho.com 

@uiwithjaeil

### **Toolkit**

**Adobe Creative Cloud:** Sketch **Adobe Photoshop** Principle Adobe Illustrator Invision Adobe InDesign Marvel

Adobe After Effects Read HTML 5 & CSS3

## **Experience**

#### **Urban FT**

UX, UI Designer

2017 - current

UX, UI design for fintech company specializing in white-label finance app solutions for banks and credit unions

Assist in end-to-end part of the UX process, from guerrilla user-testing and SPRINT sessions to UI design and customized illustrations

### **Skillset**

#### Research

**Contextual Inquiry User Interviews Affinity Mapping** Task flows **Competitive Analysis** Sitemapping

**Heurisitic Evaluations Persona Creation** 

#### **Betta Bucha LLC**

**UX Client Consultant** 

2017

UX consulting for startup specializing in locally-brewed kombucha drink

Complete re-haul of visuals, interface, and features with data analyzed through market research, user interviews and continuous iterations from user testings

#### Design

User Interface (UI) Animation Rapid Prototyping **Art Direction** Wireframing Illustration Storyboarding **Typography** Web Design **Brand Identity** 

### **Center for Employment Opportunities (CEO)**

Graphic Designer

2014 - 2016

Managed all design and marketing aspects of the non-profit with 200+employees

Created key print assets as annual reports, brochures, and budget prospectus and online assets as ads, banners and social media content.

### **Education**

### **General Assembly NY**

Certificate in UX Design Immersive

# **Cornell University**

Bachelors of Science in **Industrial Labor Relations** 

### **Freelance**

UX/UI, logo, illustration

2013 - current

#### **Clients**

Penguin Random House VOX Media - Bloody Elbow Okayplayer

**Cornell University** Sherdog MMA Mochi Magazine